[Music]
[Applause]
you know I know how to make him stop and
St as I own now the club ain't even
handle me right now watching you
watching me I go
all the club ain't even
right
[Music]
now handle me
right can't nothing H to me right now I
see you together let's get them I own
the night and I don't need no h got to
be
the
stuck for the club arogant like yeah
like money on the girls just ma one to
many yall know me like 12 hook like just
bottles modles better sh fall out cuz
that's the business all out is so
ridiculous thr out so much attention
scream out I'm in the building that they
watching I know this I'm rocking I'm
rolling I'm holding I know it you know
it know I know how to make them stop and
stare as I own now the club ain't even
handle me right now watching you
watching me I go all out the club ain't
even hand me right
[Music]
now the club a't even handle me right
now still feeling myself I'm like out of
control can't stop no more shots let's
go more rounds till I get a KO around TR
to make me P the till I can't no more
celebrate cuz that's all I know Z the
group is taking off their clothes Grand
Finale like super
go hard I run the show that's right
while I got money to blow more lights
more ice when I walk in the door no h do
a big all over the glob yeah I said it
Go Tell It Come f it who ready I'm ready
you ready let's get it know I
know make
stop now the club a even handle me right
now watching you watching me I go all
out the club can't even me right now
your hands up your hands up your hands
up even me right now put your hands up
put your hands up put your hands
up you got me watching now got my
attention now got everybody in the club
W to know now I am a l man come be my
lady and we can both s i
bring your body and let me switch up
your atmosphere take you out of the club
and up in my new L you around the world
you want baby girl are you ready to go
now know I know how to make them stop
and St my phone now the club a even
handle me right now watch you you
watching me I go all out the CLP ain't
even
right put your hands up put your hands
up put your hands up put your hands up
put your hands up let's celebrate now
put your hands up you know who shut them
down
[Music]